How is she doing this?
We captured her thundercloud, didn't we?
Kashi, Kashi!
You naughty boy!
Nobody treats me like that and
gets away with it, understand?
Listen, you miserable rodent!
You're gonna be punished for
dropping me into the sea!
and it won't be pretty.
But now, we prepare for the worst.
That old bag sure has a lot of energy.
She looks even stronger now.
Ma, ma, ma, ma!
This is no good.
We need time.
Let's retreat!
Running away?
Well, that just won't do.
You knew it! Hey, you!
Why don't you show me what you got?
Yes, Mama.
Bulbara!
Let's go.
See you
next time.
Hey, killer.
You okay?
Yeah.
Old bat.
She sent us flying a long way.
Felt like it.
But that aside, where the hell are we?
In the castle.
That's all I've got.
And where's Big Mom?
Must have lost us.
That hole she made is pretty huge.
She knows we're in here, but
she probably doesn't know where.
Little brat, get over here kid,
I won't be happy until I split you in two!
Sounds like she's below
us, down a floor or two.
We gotta try to keep her here.
If she teams up with Kaido
again, we're all dead.
I'll send her to hell.
Let's finish this!
Straw sword!
Huh?
It can't be!
Hawkins!
You traitor!
You've got some balls showing
your face in front of us!
You think I won't kill you?!
I was betrayed by Apu as well.
We aren't so different.
I merely avoided a fight that I
knew I had no chance of winning.
Well, aren't you clever?
But you need a spy to
make it off this stage.
You're so weak you knew you'd lose
before the fight even started.
Then get your ass off the battlefield!
Cause some of us are here to win!
You can't win.
You're lucky to still be alive.
Shut your damn trap.
I'm going to throw up just breathing
the same air as a coward like you.
Kid, I'll handle this.
We can't leave Big Mom unchecked.
Just go.
I'll cut him down.
Thanks, partner.
Come on!
Don't let him get away!
You're too kind.
I wouldn't stand a chance
against both of you.
Demon face.
Look at you.
Such a hard-working little headliner.
Your master must be proud.
Maybe they'll give you a treat.
Say what you want, but
they'll be your last words.
There's a 92 % chance
you'll die here after all.
Poor, poor Hitokiri Kamazon.
Fortune-telling, huh?
Well, fortune favors the bold.
Alright then, killer.
Best of luck to you.
Screw that.
You can take your luck and stuff it.
This win will be mine alone.
Are you going to run me around all day?
Because I've had enough.
Sorry, but we don't
have room for dinosaurs.
No way!
Let's do this.
Hit his weak spot, Seesop! I'm on it!
You think we're just gonna give up?
We'll keep fighting
even if it's not pretty!
First, the temple!
The chin!
The edible apple!
Damn you!
You won't stop!
Neither will we!
The apple!
The nostril too!
Get off already!
Come on, man.
How much more abuse are you going to take?
You can't be enjoying this.
Try to stay strong, Kumachi.
I'm sure we'll be there soon.
The performance floor stage
should be the perfect spot.
Where Selena and her friends
gave a whole ton of keeping Tang!
to the other generals.
On the stage, I can give all of
them an order at the same time.
Then we'll have a bunch of gifters on our
side because then I can finally be useful.
After that, you guys
won't have to protect me
because it won't matter if I die.
So get me to the stage.
How could you say that, Tama?
You're wrong.
We're here for you.
We won't stop fighting until our
friends and Wano are finally free.
Let's do this together.
You've got a beautiful young lady and
her older friend to protect you. What?
Older than who?
I'm only 19!
It's not that I don't want to fight.
I want to help people just like me. Oh!
I'm trying, but I...
I'm too scared!
I can't take it anymore!
Making an enemy out of me was
a mistake, you stupid brat!
How dare you, break that child!
I'm sorry I yelled, Tama.
You don't need to push yourself anymore.
It's time for me to finish this.
Do it, Usopp!
One lizard buster, coming right up!
I'm sick of you!
I'm going to pull that stupid nose
off your face and snap it in two!
Special attack green star, go!
Are you just doing this
crap to piss me off?
Firework flowers!
It's so hot!
Careful with that, Usopp!
Sorry, it's the best
close-range weapon I've got.
But don't worry, I'll finish him now.
Special attack!
Green Star, go!
Exploding Picoons!
Come on, Billy Yusuf!
Bullseye!
Direct hit!
Extermination complete!
You lizards got nothing on me!
Hey!
I heard that!
He got knocked down!
But he got up again!
How are we gonna keep him down?
Damn it.
I am gonna kill those idiots!
I wish Kibidongo worked on that, maniac.
It only works with Smilefruits.
But what do we do if he comes back?
Come on, kid!
Where are you?
No!
It's Big Mom!
Huh?
Weird.
I guess I'm free.
Now where's Mama? Mama! I'm here!
Where did you go?
No!
I'll find you! I'm coming!
Just wait!
Mama, please!
Why won't you answer me?
I want to help!
Did Eustace's power stop working?
I finally broke up Kaido and Big Mom.
It'll be a pain if she comes
back for that thundercloud.
Straw Hat!
I'm taking everyone downstairs
while you get Kaido! Okay.
Mama!
Having fun are you?
The more dangerous it gets, the
more that smile of yours throws.
No, no,
no,
no, no, no, no, no,
Please, Luffy!
Defeat him!
End this!
I know!
Kiku, does your shoulder hurt?
Do not ask such things of a samurai.
It is not but an itch I cannot scratch.
Much like the itch upon mine heart
that appeared the day you left home.
Izo!
Alright.
If you're well enough to
tease me, that's good news.
But I really am sorry.
I shouldn't have left without telling you.
Izo, if the land of Wano is truly opened,
how do you think the country will change?
Can't say.
If we survive, perhaps we'll
discuss it tomorrow morning.
A tall task indeed.
The island is engulfed in battle.
It's win or die.
There must be a shortage
of troops everywhere.
I am confident that I can protect
Lord Momonosuke on my own.
My opponent will surely be Kanjuro.
With any luck, I will reach Lord
Momonosuke before he finds him.
This time, Kanjuro will meet his end.
The rest of you, go help the others.
Godspeed. All right. Fare thee well.
Dear friends, let us hope that
we are all reunited soon. Yeah.
Come on.
Time's a-wasting. Right.
Good luck.
Master Keen!
This is my fault.
Allow me to fight Kanjuro again.
I won't fail.
Kiku!
Let us make haste. Of course.
Goodness!
Huh?
Greetings, Master Cat Viper!
I knew it was you!
Cecilion! Baratie!
Where are you dashing off to?
Never mind that, sir.
We could use some help.
The thing is... Pedro!
Ah, Pedro was dead?
Surely not.
Yes, he died fighting
in Big Mom's territory.
He sacrificed himself
to protect Luffy's crew.
They wouldn't be here
if it wasn't for him.
Well, Pedro, good job.
It seems Ugarra died a hero.
And the bastard responsible
for his death is here?
Uh-huh.
It would be bananas if
we let him get off easy.
He's quite formidable.
Wanda and Carrot are fighting him now.
We'll give a good thrashing for Pedro.
Where are you going? Master!
The cat's flying!
Rick!
Both of you, once I'm gone,
watch out for the Marys.
They're roaming around Onigashima,
doing recon for Kaido and his men. What?
They're here?
Where are they?
Don't worry, I made this! Huh?
It's you!
Seriously?
It's a perfect likeness!
A perfect decoy!
You're the target, but
they're looking for us both.
As long as they think we're
together, they'll come after me!
Brilliant!
Sounds like you're sick of this tiny room
and you're looking for an excuse to fight.
It's fine, Yamato.
Master King can protect us
and he's on his way here.
For now, Lord Momonosuke can count on me.
See you soon.
You've got this.
Oh, wait.
Hey, Momonosuke.
You said you could hear
Luffy's voice, right?
How is he?
It seems he's alright.
It hasn't changed from earlier.
He's not using his full strength.
Wait.
I'm hearing a second voice!
I'm sure that's Kaido.
If Luffy's fighting him
alone, this could get ugly.
I must hurry!
Everything's here.
All the details of my father's adventures.
I've heard tales of his
exploits many times over.
But to actually read his words…
Well, I'll be the cat burglar
and the long-nosed fool.
She's gonna do us!
Did Straw Hat bring the whole new crew?
Hi, Elaine!
Oh, Otama!
I'm so happy to see you.
But this place is very dangerous.
Why in the world would you come here?
I've been worried about you
since we split up, Olie.
You just disappeared back in New Dawn.
Oh, I...
I'm sorry, dear.
It's a scary world for a little girl,
and I've been worried about you, too.
Don't worry, I'm not mad.
I'm just happy to see you again.
I never got to thank you properly.
You took care of me when I lost my memory.
Woo-hoo!
That means you got it back!
That's wonderful!
Uh-huh.
Oh, no.
Mama went into mother mode.
This happens every time
since around kids under 10.
Whoa!
Let's be careful, Otama!
I think they're friends somehow!
That kimono looks great on you!
You think so?
See my hair head?
It's cute, too!
Oshiriko, make her go away!
Say, that woman who did my hair before.
Uh, she was a real busybody.
Lived in Okobore town.
Seemed really poor.
Oh, Otsuru, right?
How's she doing these days?
I'll never forget my first taste
of Oshiriko that lovely day.
It's so yummy!
I wish I could eat it again.
Something happened, actually.
Huh?
Teokobore Town, I mean.
It's all gone now.
Gone?
What do you mean by that?
The people there lied and said
they stole food from Kaido.
But it was actually the samurai
who took it before the raid.
But Kaido's men didn't think twice.
They burned down the whole town that day!
Here, Olin.
Goodness! Heavenly!
They're rebels!
Don't let them get away!
Burn them along with the town!
Not just the houses, but people too.
Otsuru.
You look gorgeous, Olin.
You're going to love it.
I can't wait!
It's so cute!
Kaido's men killed them!
Don't let them get away!
Burn them along with the town!
We were strangers But they cared
for me When I lost my memory
Bye, O 'Nein
Those poor people
They had so little In Hokobori
town But they shared with me anyway
And you rewarded them with death?
I totally forgot about the lizard guy!
Buzz off!
We're busy now!
Komachiyo, let's go, boy!
Hey, big boss!
Don't let those little
cowards get past you!
Let's run!
Must go faster!
Too slow!
Time to say goodbye!
You spineless coon.
We pirates live in a world
of villainy and vice,
but we still have honor and justice.
Damn you!
You bastard!
Oh, bitch!
That was her!
It has to be!
It's Mama!
I'm so happy she saved him!
Are you okay, Kuma Gio?
We gotta keep going!
Thank you.